# Raheem Richardson

123 Windermere Rd., Seattle, WA 12345 raheemrichardson@ example.com (123) 456-7890

A Lead Mall Security Guard with 10+ years of experience, specializing in surveillance, security operations, conflict resolution, and communication. A proven track record of providing superior customer service and ensuring the safety of patrons during store hours.

### **Education**

High School Diploma
Roosevelt High School, Seattle, WA
September 2008 - June 2012

## **Key Skills**

- **♦** Conflict Resolution
- De-Escalation Techniques
- Communication
- Security Management
- Customer Service

#### **Certifications**

- Guard Card License #12345, State of Washington, 2012
- CPR Certified, Red Cross, 2012

## **Professional Experience**

Lead Mall Security Guard
Westline Mall, Seattle, WA I June 2016 - Present

- Identify peaceful resolutions to emergency situations using de-escalation techniques to ensure customer safety, prevent bodily harm, and detain suspects without violence
- Lead a team of 15+ mall security guards to perform daily patrols for unusual behavior and potential security threats and ensure adherence to conflict resolution protocols
- Provide training to team members in security operations, safety protocols, communication procedures, and de-escalation techniques

#### Mall Security Guard

North West Mall Seattle, WA | September 2012 - June 2016

- Coordinated security operations for a mall with 200+ daily patrons, interfaced with the general public to de-escalate stressful situations and prevent conflict, and ensured compliance with security protocols and safety procedures
- Oversaw access control for restricted areas of the mall and store property, which included identifying irregular behaviors and performing security checks